turns on yes yes yes that's it that's what
включается да да да во вот оно оно то
look here he said moderno zisk and
смотрите вот он сказал модерно зыску и
then like well the
дальше типа ну включается
movie turns on there aliens on whom there on
фильм вот там пришельцы на кого там на
avatar are dropping something now
аватара скидывают сейчас что-то
we talked about a starship recently well yes we didn't
звездолёта общались недавно ну да не
find any common contacts
нашли общих общих контактов
and what do you think we'll find now
а как думаете сейчас найдём
well in principle here you can find
ну в принципе сюда можно найти точки
common ground for
соприкосновения
example
например
well if there is a desire
ну если есть желание
desire let's try to wish
желание давайте попробуем пожелать
let's what were the last movies you
давайте какие последние фильмы вам
liked
нравились
robert madyar series jagajaga
роберт мадиар сериал джагаджага
yeah so what else not with you somehow
угу так какие ещё не с вы как-то так
hooked you haven't heard of this director no no I haven't
хукнули вы не слышали этого режиссёра не
heard are
не не слышал
you sure you want to talk about the movie well
вы точно о фильма хотите поговорить
maybe something interesting will interest
ну может что-то интересное заинтересует
me yes it's very interesting objective
меня да это очень интересно объективный
realism
реализм
so well I'll record it for myself to
так ну я себе запишу его чтобы
watch
посмотреть
so you can put something else on it's not that
так ещё можно что-нибудь поставить не
I'll advertise a little
дело в том что я немножко порекламирую
if it's just that I'm a fan I'm a fan he uh he has a
если вот просто я фанат я фанат он ээ у
concept uh
него концепция
one day one episode is called very
ээ один день одна серия называется очень
short episodes there are 5 minutes maybe a
короткие серии там 5 минут может быть
maximum of 15 that's objective realism and
максимум 15 вот объективный реализм и у
he has a method called a series
него есть метод называется сериал
disposable actors that is the principle:
одноразовых актёров то есть принцип:
let the actors not be very famous
пусть актёры будут не сильно знаменитые
but they should not be
но они не должны
repeated from episode to episode if the actor
повторяться из серии в серию если актёр
played in this plot 5 10 15 minutes
поиграл в этом сюжете 5 10 15 минут всё
more he does not appear in any episode
больше он ни в одной серии не
quite interesting because
появляется довольно интересно потому что
well this is by the way an interesting approach yes this is a
ну это кстати интересный подход да это
large rotation of actors and for actors
большая ротация актёров и для актёров
this is a practice in principle this is
это практика в принципе это очень даже
not bad at all well
не неплохо
yes the thing is that here it
ну да дело в том что тут больше ещё
turns out that
получается что
uh so much when he started working
ээ настолько когда начинал он работать
yes there were no problems with actors yes you
да не было проблемов с актёрами да ты
found it once you found it but it turns out
раз раз нашёл нашёл но получается из-за
because the actors are disposable such a
того что актёры одноразовые такая
concept after two that's how long he's been
концепция на после двух вот сколько он
filming films for about 2 years these are the
уже там 2 года где-то снимает фильмы эти
problem of the actor's whining moreover
проблема ныти актёра больше того начался
this genre began it became popular and uh other
этот жанр он стал популярным и ээ другие
directors also began to copy him well that
режиссёры тоже начинают его копировать
is he was one of the
ну то есть он как был один из
founders of this genre that is there were
родоначальников этого жанра то есть были
other people who tried to film in
ещё люди которые пробовали снимать в
this style but he just somehow became
этом стиле но он просто как-то стал
very popular to him on the development uh
очень популярный ему на развитии ээ вот
these on the set of films even he began to
эти на съёмке фильмов начали даже он
collect money at first uh they said that
собирать деньги сначала ээ говорили
he would like grants from the state  he applied
чтобы он типа гранты от госно подавал
but he started posting his
вот но он начал выкладывать ээ в
series on the internet and people started
интернете свои эти сериалы и люди начали
donating he said: "if you want
скидывать он говорил: "если хотите
us to release more
больше чтобы мы регулярнее выпускали
videos more regularly so that they last longer and are more interesting, donate
видео чтобы дольше интереснее скидывайте
for equipment for the
на аппаратуру на состав съёмочной
crew" and really people he had a
группы" и реально люди он короче было у
fundraising campaign he had 30
него фандрейзинговая компания была он 30
million hryvnia that's like almost a million
млн гривен это короче типа почти миллион
dollars his first fundraising
долларов было первая его фандрейзинговая
campaign they raised something in 2 days they
компания собрали что-то за 2 дня за 2
raised in 2 days that is well it's about the same as
дня собрали то есть ну это примерно как
modern YouTubers who need to
современные ютуберы которым нужно
donate well here it's a little different that is
донатить ну тут немножко другое то есть
he had a concept like we were
у него концепция такая что вот мы
collecting specifically for equipment
собирал он конкретно на аппаратуру был
there was a list of equipment that we would buy
ээ список аппаратуры что мы закупим вот
for this studio for the set for
на эту студию на съёмочную площадку на
uh props for training these operators
ээ реквизит на обучение этих операторов
that is like that
то есть вот так
yeah and he really likes Robert Madyar
угу и реально любится роберт мадяр
that's
это
his pseudonym like director's so
его псевдоним типа режиссёрский так у
his last name is Brovdi and so his
него фамилия бровди а так у него
director's pseudonym is Robert Madyar
режиссёрский псевдоним роберт мадяр всё
I found everything I wrote down for myself yeah definitely he has uh
нашёл я себе записал да да обязательно у
well, like, uh, objective
него ээ ну такой как бы ээ объективный
realism, interesting series from series, they are not
реализм интересные серия от серии они не
connected, that is, not that one series is a
соединены то есть не то что одна серия
continuation, a swarm, it happens, it happens that there is a
продолжениярой бывает бывает такое что
continuation, but basically, for
продолжение а в основном у него вот там
example, there are worms there, yes, like some uh,
например есть черви да как некоторые ээ
such creatures, they kind of burrow into the
такие существа они как бы закапываются в
ground, crawl out, uh, in short, they do
землю вылазят ээ короче типа делают
all sorts of nasty things, like they are, like,
всякие гадости типа они вот типа
aliens and they need to be burned, in
пришельцы и их нужно выжечь вот там
short, damn, you can't convey this, there are all sorts of things, yeah,
короче блин не передать это всякое есть
and let's suppose if, well, in your opinion,
а предположим если ну и по вашему мнению
that is, I have
то есть у меня складывается на
the opinion today that modern
сегодняшний день мнение что современные
films are like that, then they
фильмы они такие какие-то потом что-то
turned on something or that
включали или что
no, I didn't understand, they always turned on something and
нет не понял всё что-то включали и
admired it, it
улюбувались мне
seems to me, no, that's what I had the feeling
кажется не нет вот мне мне такое чувство
that most modern films are like
показалось что современные фильмы
that, they are disposable, you watch them
большинство они такие одноразовые
and forget about them, but
посмотрел и забыл а вот старые фильмы
sometimes I
порой некоторые там девяностых годов мне
really want to rewatch old films, some of the nineties, well, that's
прямо очень хочется пересматривать ну
because, look, I'll tell you,
это потому что смотрите я я скажу что
why is it that in the nineties, it
почему дело в том что в девяностых вот
was like a newspaper, yes, a newspaper was published,
было как газета да выходила газета у
my grandfather, he made it into a file, and he
меня дед он её в подшивку делал и он её
reread it once  in a month he reread old newspapers
перечитывал раз в месяц он старые газеты
because there were no new and
перечитывал потому что не было новых и
as if media now already
как бы средств информации сейчас уже
old films they are not interesting the thing is
старые фильмы они неинтересны дело в том
that the flow of films is so new and the plot and
что поток фильмов такой новый и сюжета и
we are yesterday's even here with this Robert
мы вчерашний даже вот у этого роберта
Madyar if you haven't watched a week of series
мадяра если ты не посмотрел неделю серии
you don't watch the old ones you already watch the
ты не смотришь старые ты уже смотришь
new ones because it's no longer relevant to you uh the
новые потому что тебе уже не актуально
plot that was that is there is something new
ээ сюжет который был то есть есть новое
you always want something new so the old no well
ты хочешь всегда нового так что старый
modern no modern films
не ну современ нет современные фильмы
they are just so predictable that's
просто они настолько предсказуемые вот
how much I watch once I watched and that's it
сколько я не смотрю один раз посмотрел и
you Roberton is unpredictable in short
всё вы робертона непредсказуемый короче
Robert Madyar had such that means
у роберта мадяра было такой значит
uh also here he like the genre of fantasy like
ээ тоже вот он типа жанр фэнтези типа
makes but objective realism but as a
делает но объективный реализм но как
fantasy what does it mean the creature some kind of
фэнтези что значит существо какие-то
aliens
пришельцы
they don't know where they came from
они не знаю откуда они прибыли
settled in short they have some kind of
расположились короче у них какая-то э
alien or base or whatever and
инопланетная или база или что была и
launched the zone how this alien was knocked out
запускали зон как этого инопланетянина
there was such a tower on this
вырубили там была такая башня на эту
tower a special reconnaissance apparatus landed
башню разведывательный аппарат сел
and this alien
специальный и этот инопланетянин
alien he like climbed the tower that is
пришелец он типа полез на башню то есть
he saw that something there  uh
он увидел что что-то там ээ инородное
some foreign body flew in he climbed climbed in
тело какое-то прилетело он полез полез
short and he uh took it with his hand already climbed out onto
короче и он ээ взял рукой уже вылез на
this tower to the very end uh there is such an
эту башню в самый конец ээ там такая
intrigue in short well what will happen what will happen and in
интрига короче ну что будет что будет и
short he touches this device and this
короче он трогает этот аппарат а этот
device was mined it
аппарат был заминирован он короче
explodes and this
взрывается и этот
alien from it in short all this pours you
пришелец с него короче всё это льётся
know he hangs like that and he begins
знаешь он так свисает и он начинает там
such a plot there is just well damn awesome not
такой сюжет просто ну блин офигенный не
just fell but there is a tower when you climb
просто упал а там башня когда залазишь
there are such
там такие
brackets that you kind of climb between them and
скобы что ты как бы меж ними лезешь и за
hold on to them and he begins this
них держишься и он начинает этот
alien this body falls for these brackets
пришелец это тело падаться за это скобы
beats gets tangled and he in short and at the end he
бьётся путается и он короче и в конце он
falls and a meter from the ground so uh hangs like that
падает и в метре от земли так э свисает
all torn up damn that's the
вот это такой весь подранный блин это
plot really I will never come in life there would be no such
сюжет вот реально не приду в жизни не
thing like how they filmed it it's
было бы такого вот как они это сняли
just cool
просто это кайф
it reminded me of this alien there are
это мне примерно напомнил этот чужой вот
four episodes there he has a
четыре серии вот там вот у него очень
lot in the style of alien there are really a lot of
много в стиле чужого там реально чужих
these aliens like all sorts they really
этих куча типа всяких есть они реально
destroy them they like I don't know  they come from somewhere I don't
их уничтожают они как не знаю откуда-то
know how they multiply they
берутся не знаю они как вот плодятся
multiply there is something there that uh a
плодятся там есть такое что
dude was sitting that means uh a warrior uh of the
ээ чувак сидел это значит ээ воин ээ
alliance and he uh with a special
альянса и он ээ специальным таким
weapon he exterminated these aliens and they
оружием он истреблял этих чужих а они
stupidly like this you know like zombies
тупо вот таким знаешь как как зомбаки
in short they crawled out of
короче вылазили типа ни
nowhere scary well quite an interesting
отткуда стрёмно ну довольно интересная
story so I literally about a year
история вот я вот я буквально где-то год
ago I decided I thought let's watch
назад я решил думаю давай посмотрю
alien and I think as far as I remember well the
чужого и я думаю я насколько помню вот
second part or the third I
вот вторая мне часть или третья
remember and then I saw it turns out there is the
запомнилась а потом увидел оказывается
first part of some eighty-
есть первая часть какого-то восемьдесят
seventh year I thought damn something scary to
седьмого года думаю блин что-то стрёмно
watch and when I started watching I saw
смотреть а когда начал смотреть увидел
old filming but the plot of the film is
съёмки старые но сюжет фильма ну
so awesome and so old
настолько офигительный и вот старые
films seem to me they put well
фильмы мне кажется они закладывают вот
how can I say it they put your soul into it that it's
ну как это сказать душу закладывают что
just interesting to watch but
просто интересно смотреть а вот
modern films are beautifully filmed I will
современные фильмы красиво снят я я же
say well not to put your soul into it I
скажу ну не то что душу закладывать я
remember this in childhood when we watched
помню это в детстве когда мы смотрели
it just in the evening on a black and white
это как раз вечер был на чёрно-белом
TV we were watching this alien and there is a
телевизоре смотрели вот это чужой и там
moment when uh from the stomach of this woman this
момент когда э из живота этой тёт эта
crap  jumped out not that I was soulful hall I
фигня выскочила не то что душу зал я
really almost it really was now you are
реально чуть не это реально было сейчас
watching for example now you are watching
смотришь например вот сейчас смотришь
Madyar he has such a style that
мадяр у него такая значит стилистика что
he should not scare his viewer here in
он не должен пугать своего зрителя вот в
someone else's director he scared his viewer
чужом режиссёр он пугал своего зрителя
yes and here on the contrary you he shows such
да а тут наоборот ты он показывает такие
horror films there is such a mess but the viewer
ужастики там такое месиво но зритель
gets inspiration that is I mean no matter how much I
получает вдохновление то есть я сколько
watched this Robert
не смотрел вот это роберта
Modnyar there is blood exploding heads
модняра там разрывается кровь головы
fly off everything in short you know such
отлетают всё короче знаешь тако
annihilation by and never was there a moment
аннигиляция по икогда не было момента
that I experienced fear goodness warmth in the
что я испытал страх благость теплоту на
soul was but fear no
душе было но страх нет
all the same here again when now I will
всё равно вот опять же когда вот сейчас
say horror films they somehow
скажу ужасы фильмы они нас как-то
prepare us turn on a special background
подготавливают включают специальный фон
some kind of calm music and then
какую-то музыку такую спокойную и потом
suddenly bam a person automatically gets scared
резко ба человек автоматически пугается
in this case maybe he really
в этом случае может он действительно
made such an approach where he does not connect
сделал такой подход где он не подключает
any special effects that affect the
какие-то спецэффекты которые влияют на
psyche of a person who a person is
психи человека который человек
prepared look he does not have
подготовлен смотри у него у него нету
some kind of specialized
какого-то вот специализированного
musical accompaniment yes that is
музыкального сопровождения да то есть
here you are right that is he has more
вот тут вы правы то есть у него более
like uh real but it seems like it is like
как бы ээ реально а вот оно вроде как
documentary but it seems to be
похоже на документалку но вроде
fiction so that is, there is no such
художественный так то есть нету вот этой
big artistic processing
слишком большой художественной обработки
there is musical everything yes that is
там музыкальной всё да вот в этом есть
why it is not scary it is clear there is no tension
поэтому она не пугает видно там не накал
yes
не делает да
yes maybe people are ready for
да возможно у него как бы люди готовы к
it they are already calm about it well yes
этому уже спокойно к этому относятся ну
that is approximately I have yes yes I had
да то есть примерно у меня вот да у меня
approximately the same fear when it came out
примерно такой же страх был когда вылез
this is me when I was playing in Dendy let's apply to
это я когда в денди играл приложем на
some boss I jumped out and that
босса какого-то выскочил вот и вот этот
same fear I also had yeah got it yeah
же страх у меня тоже бывал угу понял ну
there uh let's say this Hungarian guy he has
да там ээ скажем вот этого мадяра вот
very unbelievable names
очень не как бы невероятные названия у
you think how that the film
него вот вы считаете как что вот фильм
should reflect uh what is happening in it
должен отображать ээ то что в нём
in the title
происходит в название
I will say so right now roughly speaking I just
я так скажу вот сейчас грубо говоря я
arrived in Krasnodar as a guest
сейчас вот приехал в краснодар как гость
yeah and I don't know this city I
угу и я этот город не знаю я вчера
saw a restaurant yesterday called
увидел ресторан который называется
Ballerina and
балерина и
Beefsteak and for me there was an explosion what kind of how could such a
бифштекс и для меня случился взрив что
restaurant be called
за как вот такой ресторан могли назвать
Ballerina and Beefsteak they have a signature
балерина и бифштекс они же есть подпись
and a name culture is in everyone and for
и название культура есть в каждом и для
me this meaning was revealed that well
меня вот этот смысл открылся что ну
roughly
грубо
speaking Beefs is well that  as usual they
говоря бифкс - это ну вот как обыденно
eat, everyone just eats, but everyone has a culture,
жрут все просто жрут но культура вот у
even in spite of who eats this
каждого даже несмотря на кто жрёт этот
bisnex, even a burger, it's interesting to
бишнекс даже бургер интересно там
watch ballet there, and for me, here's a restaurant,
посмотреть балет и для меня вот ресторан
well, it somehow played differently, the beauty that they
ну как-то по-другому заиграл крас что
really put some meaning into it, and
действительно вложили смысл какой-то и
if they put some meaning into the title,
если вот в название укладывают какой-то
where you just need to think and not
смысл где нужно просто подумать а не
just a table of contents, that's really
просто оглавление вот это действительно
cool when he does something like that,
кайф когда вот делает что-то такое
for example, uh, Robert Madyar had
например ээ у роберта мадяра вот серия
one episode called, for example, the pursuit of the
одна называлась например погона за
pursuit of the loaf, and the second episode
погоня за за буханкой и вторая серия
was called find the ninja, what do you think,
называлась найти ниндзю как вы думаете
what was in the first episode, uh, the pursuit of
вот что было в первой ээ серии погоня за
the loaf, for example, what could have been, and
буханкой например что могло быть
again,
а это опять же
he is the director of what country, so I'll ask, he
он режиссёр какой страны так я спрошу он
himself, uh, from Transcarpathia, from Ukraine, he is from yes, yes, ah, well,
сам ээ из закарпатья из украины он родом
I understand, well, if so,
да да а а ну я я понял ну если так
because in my opinion, loaves are just
потому что в моёмходе буханки это как
these old loaf cars
раз-таки старые вот эти машины буханки
that drove, damn, you really
которые ездили вы блин вы реально вы
guessed shrewdly, yes, indeed,
проницательно угадали да действительно
because I usually, if Russians
потому что я обычно если вот россияне
usually have a loaf  - this is a loaf of bread yes
обычно буханка - это буханка хлеба да
perception yes but you can see you are really
восприе да а вот вы вот видно вы реально
well a fan of the film really
ну почитатель фильма действительно да
yes well for me this yes a
ну вот у меня вот это
loaf these are still cars yes then there
да буханка это всё-таки машины да то там
was just well such a gist that these
была просто ну такая суть что вот эти
aliens they like uh captured this
пришельцы они типа ээ захватили эту
loaf and they moved on this
буханку так и они передвигались на этой
loaf and it turns out it was necessary to catch up with
буханке и получается нужно было догнать
them and eliminate them like there a little well it's
их и ликвидировать типа там немножко вот
interesting yes here is the pursuit of a loaf
ну интересно да вот погоня за буханкой
like and you look like you think like well
типа и ты так смотришь такой думаешь
now they will fight for bread yes
типа ну сейчас за хлебом будут биться да
and there in short these aliens are really
а там короче реально этих пришельцев
destroyed because they
типа уничтожают потому что они это в
move in this loaf yes so what
буханке этой передвигаются да так что
was damn yes yes and if again the hunt for
было блин да да а если опять же охота за
ninja is correct or was called the hunt for zanie well for
ниндй правильно или назвали охота зани
me probably the hunt for myself it
ну у меня наверное охота за самим собой
seems to me a ninja is like a shadow and well and well
мне кажется ниндзя это как тень а вот и
approximately such associations
ну примерно такие у меня ассоциации
arose for me there was yes there was just so
возникли было да там было просто значит
this alien he was in such a suit that
этот пришелец он был в таком костюме то
is he was all black
есть он чёрный весь был не было видно
his eyes were not visible and as if he was in the form of a ninja
его глаз и как бы он был в образе нинзии
he controlled flying machines of
он управлял летающими аппаратами вот
these  aliens and there was some kind of forest,
этих пришельцев и там был лес какой-то
well, I don't know, enchanted or
такой ну он не знаю заколдованный или
something like that, and this ninja, he was constantly
что типа его и этот ниндзя он постоянно
moving, constantly moving, but he was
перемещался постоянно перемещал но он
like the main one controlling these
типа был главный по управлению вот этими
alien devices and they
пришельческими аппаратами и его
tried to eliminate him,
пробовали ликвидировать
say, catch him, catch him, there were worms that
скажем поймать выловить там черви его
protected him, like, there were also worms,
защищали типа ещё там ну черви-то почти
they appear in almost every episode, well, he
в каждой серии они появляются ну он
likes to insert these worms, like, it's already
любит этих червей типа вставлять уже
a little boring, yes, he probably took them from a dune, yes, well, I do
немножко приелось да из из дюны наверное
n't know, or from a dune,
взял да да ну вот не знаю или из дюны
or, apparently, there are a lot of actors, you know,
или ну видно актёров много есть знаешь
who want to play all this there, and so,
которые там хотят это всё сыграть вот и
uh, with this ninja, in short, the ninja there, on the
ээ с этим ниндзьй короче ниндзю там с
fifth or seventh try, in general, they
пятого или седьмого раза в общем
still managed to kill them, they killed the ninja there, uh,
всё-таки завалили завалили ниндзю там ээ
they requested help from
запрашивали подмогу из звездолёта
some kind of starship so that they could also hit this ninja, in short, from afar, with
какого-то чтобы тоже этого ниндзю короче
something, from some kind of
издалека чем-то били какой-то от
star artillery or something like that, and
звёздной артиллерии или что типа и в
so, in the end, they killed this ninja,
общем так и замочили этого ниндз в
but he was tenacious, yeah,
результате но он живучий был угу
that's the fantasy genre, fantasy for me  he
вот фэнтези жанр фэнтези для меня он
always
всегда
seemed well by nature I generally really
казался ну я по природе вообще очень
like historical films
люблю всё-таки исторические фильмы
documentaries or those based on
документальные либо на основаны на
real events that is when I see
реальных событиях то есть я когда вижу
some titles I immediately jump out:
какие-то названия у меня сразу кидается:
"oh this is the one I want to watch" and
"о вот этот я хочу посмотреть" а к
I always treated fantasy well well this is a
фэнтези я всегда относился ну так ну это
one-time thing but really there are such
на один раз но действительно есть такие
films when you immerse yourself in them and are
фильмы когда погружаешься в них и
stunned how cool here is the same Avatar
офигеваешь как классно вот тот же аватар
that is just imagine this
то есть просто представить вот эту
other planet Pandora where they live
другую планету пандору где живут вот
look why why I love this I
смотри за что за что я люблю этого я
Avatar is also Hungarian he sometimes takes
аватар тоже мадяра он он берёт иногда
some characters from famous
некоторых персонажей из известных
films and plays them in his plots
фильмов э обыгрывает их в своих сюжетах
here he also has avatars he has
вот у него аватары тоже есть у него есть
worms there are avatars yes but his avatars
черви есть аватары да но у него аватары
they are negative yes here the avatar was he is
они негативные да вот тут аватар был он
like a positive character yes and here his avatar is
типа позитивный персонаж да а тут аватар
negative that is the avatar is also an
у него негативный то есть аватар тоже
alien and the avatar these forces of
есть пришельцем и аватара вот эти силы
good they eliminate him and there are
добра они его ликвидируют причём
a lot of avatars there are
аватаров там много есть
whole ones let's say there is such a thing
есть целые прям вот скажем есть такое
that in the alien division
что в подразделении пришельцев кто-то
someone can be an avatar and others are such
один может быть аватаром а другие такие
fighters of the empire and there is such a thing that whole
бойцы империи а есть такое что целые
units of avatars so they behave very
подразделение из аватаров так они очень
specifically they immediately
специфично себя ведут у них там сразу
see where they landed there the
видно короче где они высадились там
landscape immediately changes well such in the
сразу ландшафт меняется ну такое
avatar way it's all somehow like that
по-аватарски оно всё как-то вот есть
yes
такое да
and now I'll say probably I could be wrong
а сейчас скажу наверное я могу ошибаться
but either someone and probably they gave after all
но либо кто-то и наверное дали всё-таки
when he painted his pictures here he
вот когда он рисовал свои картины вот он
used something they say such a thing that I
что-то употреблял говорят такое что я
think that many many of them
думаю что много много из них что-то
used something like yes Hungarian yes by the way they
употребляли типа да мадяр вот да его
ask him what like do you
кстати его вот спрашивают что типа ээ вы
like to use during filming he
любите употреблять во время съёмок он
says that candy is like a candy
говорит что цукерок это типа конфетка
in Ukrainian yes yes he sometimes for filming like
по-украински да да он бывает за съёмки
for short filming those few of
типа вот за короткие съёмки те несколько
these candies like he eats different
этих конфеток типа съедает там разные
ones and different candies and candies there
причём разные конфетки и цукерки
is such a thing I don't know what
есть такое я не знаю что
all the content is interesting to understand
все содержание интересно понять вот
what kind of fantasy people have
какая когда бывает у людей фантазия
or this happens and how is it
такая либо это бывает а как есть такое
there is a proverb of the general the random number generator became the champion in
там пословица генера чемпионом по
female logic
женской логике стал генератор случайных
random  numbers yes here he is too yes here
чисел случайных чисел да вот он тоже да
he can also turn on so
вот у него тоже может включается так
today there will be an avatar in green color
сегодня будет аватар зелёном цвете
which will say hello that is a set of some
который привёт то есть набор каких-то
words just a generator collects and he
слов просто генератор собирает и он из
makes a film out of it got it damn listen
этого делает фильм понял блин слушайте
maybe take it now maybe google
может возьмите сейчас может загуглить
I'm interested in some series now we'll
мне интересно какую-то серию сейчас
discuss with you do you have a computer yes
обсудим с вами у вас есть же компьютер
nearby or a phone well on the phone there is
да рядом или телефон ну на телефоне есть
I found it now but it came out to me on
я сейчас нашёл но он мне вышел на
youtube well for some reason and on
youtube ну на почему-то а на ютбе да на
youtube yes on youtube it's not a film that is it's just
ютбе это не фильм то есть это просто
also like a discussion don't take robert
тоже как обсуждение не возьмите роберт
madyar jagad jaga robert not robert
мадиар джагад джага роберт не роберт
madyak that's what I wrote that's what I
мадяк вот это я и написал вот я это и
wrote and he gave me youtube and this is
написал и он мне выдал youtube а это
visible but well show me again yes
видно а вот ну покажите ещё раз да
youtube well click yes that's it probably
youtube ну нажмите да это оно наверное
there first he starts telling
там он сначала он начинает рассказывать
and then this video sequence turns on well this
а потом включается вот это ээ видеоряд
turns on yes yes
ну вот такое включается
yes that's it
да да да во вот оно оно то
look here he said modernism I'm looking for and
смотрите вот он сказал модерно зыскую и
then like well the
дальше типа ну включается
film turns on there aliens who are they
фильм вот там пришельцы на кого там на
throwing at the avatar now  something of a starship
аватара скидыют сейчас что-то звездолёта
or not it turns out here it goes
или нет это тут получается он идёт
literally 3 seconds it seems to me something is wrong
буквально 3 секунд это что-то не то мне
and what again the beginning turn on and
кажется а что ещё раз начало включите и
look maybe these are pirated short films
посмотрите может это короткометражки
and they posted it no to me it
пиратские и выложили его нет мне мне
seems to me they just inserted its
кажется это просто они вставили его
name look again damn here
название вот вот смотри блин ещё раз вот
where its name is watch the whole
где его название просмотри полностью
video you unfold it for me and that's exactly it
ролик ты же мне разворачиваешь и как раз
I say here I turn on this at the
так я говорю вот я включаю вот это на
beginning everything here look look here
начало идёт всё вот смотри смотри вот
once here where he
раз вот где он
goes here he is standing with a flag this he turns on
идёт вот он с флагом стоит это он
this his insert always and
включает это его вставочка всегда а
right after the insert what well
сразу после ставочки что
and then these are some military
ну а дальше вот это военные какие-то
actions there are videos so this is not a
действия идут ролики так это не это же
film this is a piece from a film it is obvious they
фильм это кусок из фильма видно
inserted or maybe but again there should be a
вставили а может быть но опять же должен
channel then take a channel
быть тогда канал быть возьми канал
look take Robert Madyar maybe maybe these are
посмотри возьми роберт мадяр может бы
some pirated these you know
может это какие-то пиратские эти знаешь
clips they take 30 seconds each maybe yes
вырезки они берут по 30 секунд может да
I have a feeling that they just
у меня такое чувство что у него просто
inserted his name to
его вставили имя чтобы как на хейте
raise the hate maybe yes well now I often
поднять может быть да ну сейчас часто
practice this yes yes well I in any
такое практикую да да ну я в любом
case I myself  I recorded it before going to bed,
случае я себе записал я так перед сном
I'll watch the series, well, I'll watch it now, damn, it's
глянуш серии а ну я сейчас посмотрю блин
there, I'm watching it, well, I
есть же он я же его смотрю ну я его
found it on YouTube now,
вот сейчас на ютбе нашёл
so bns
так bns
194 subscribers, there are 194 subscribers, no,
194 подписчика есть 194 подписчика не
he must have more,
что-то больше должно быть у него
yeah, and such, here's a minute and a half, 3
да ну и такие тут полтора минуты 3
minutes, but Magyar, just click, yeah,
минуты а вот мадяр просто нажми да у
he has a channel called Magyar, here's a channel on
него канал называется мадяр вот канал на
YouTube called Magyar,
ютубе называется мадяр
yeah, 194,000 subscribers, yeah, that's it,
да 194.000 подписчиков
well, here's the first ones, I'm watching, there's a
да вот и есть ну вот первые смотрю вот
minute and a half, here's Twix, yes, Twix is a
там полтора минуты вот твикс да твикс
peacemaker, yeah, yeah, that's it,
миротворчий да да да вот вот это оно ну
yeah, well, I'll turn it on now,
угу ну вот сейчас включу
turn it on, about you, such realistic
включите о выте реалистические такие
filming, then something falls, yeah, now,
съёмки потом падает что-то да сейчас
look, it's going to explode, what are
сейчас смотри сейчас взорвётся
these aliens below, I see, I'm
что вово этих пришельцев внизу вижу я
also watching this video,
тоже смотрю этот ролик
parallel to the PC, it's in Russian, here's
параллельно пк это по-русски вот такой
this worm
этот червячный
warehouse, an area larger than a football
склад площальше футбольного
field,
поля
by the way, d vantazhili and a fold, with
прочим д вантажилки и складка
your efforts, they collected money for two
вашими зусиллями зібрали кошти на два
such complexes, debut  first you see
таких комплекса дебют першого вы бачите
on the other chabran this is he says that
на другом чабран это он говорит что
thanks to everyone who chipped in for
спасибо всем кто там скидывается на
equipment
аппаратуру
this work let's dance
этот хробочня потанцуем
he doesn't post everything on youtube
у него не всё на youtube выкладывает
because youtube doesn't allow
потому что там youtube не пропускает
such a genre in telegram it also blocks yes
такой жанр в телеграме ещ блокирует да
yes ok I'll run
да хорошо побегу
la all the best it was nice to meet a
ла всего хорошего приятно было встретить
person with whom you can
человека с которым можно искусствие
warm up art because here mostly hangs out so
погреть а то тут в основном тусит так
not without them thank you see you again
что не и не без них спасибо увидимся ещё
good like comment subscribe
хорошо лайк коммент подписочка
I love these movie buffs so much when they
я так люблю этих киноманов когда они
start talking about movies let's
начинают о фильмах поговорить давайте
people donate to the channel throw in for such a
народ донати на канал закиньте за такий
collapse
развал
just price new channel subscribe to it
просто це новий канал підпишись на него
right now supplier to receive
прямо зараз поставник чтоб отримати у
notifications we will be on the link
сповіщеня будем на зв'язку